<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Camp on Careless Lisper</title>
    <link>http://ryanking.com/categories/camp/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Camp on Careless Lisper</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2016 Ryan King</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2016 12:32:44 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://ryanking.com/categories/camp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>On Campers and Counselors</title>
      <link>http://ryanking.com/blog/on-campers-and-counselors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2016 12:32:44 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ryanking.com/blog/on-campers-and-counselors/</guid>
      <description>When someone scans your items at the supermarket or brings your food at a restaurant, it is an easy assumption that those people are simply doing their jobs; it&amp;rsquo;s rare to find someone who is passionate about scanning groceries or low-level work in the food service industry. When it comes to the job of camp counseling, most would probably assume the same thing: it&amp;rsquo;s just the means to a paycheck. For some that may be true, but for many, myself included, the paycheck is not the ends, rather, it is merely a way to justify spending two months at camp to those who &amp;ldquo;don&amp;rsquo;t get camp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Work as a Camp Counselor</title>
      <link>http://ryanking.com/blog/why-i-work-as-a-camp-counselor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2016 13:55:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ryanking.com/blog/why-i-work-as-a-camp-counselor/</guid>
      <description>As the counting of weeks before camp turns into the counting of days before camp, I&amp;rsquo;ve spent a lot of time reflecting on my choice to spend a second summer as a counselor at a sleep away camp. I believe it comes down to the fact that camp is, to explain mathematically, the &amp;ldquo;absolute value&amp;rdquo; of college; the majority of the positives of college are present at camp, and a majority of the inverses of the negatives of college are also present at camp.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>